blesta.com 2008-12-17

# Blesta » Privacy

## Privacy Policy - Last Revised August 4, 2006

This privacy policy is provided to demonstrate our strict commitment to customer privacy. The purpose of this statement is to explain the different types of information we collect, how we collect it, how it is used, and how it may be disclosed to others.

The protections ensured by this Privacy Policy apply only to information supplied by customers directly to Phillips Data and do not apply to communications customers may engage with third parties through any service provided by Phillips Data.

## The Collection and Use of Personally Identifiable Information

The only personally identifiable information Phillips Data collects about customers is information supplied voluntarily by the customer. Generally, personally identifiable information will not be shared with third parties for any purpose. Phillips data collects personally identifiable information for normal business purposes, to deliver products and services, administer customer accounts, and provide customer support.

Phillips Data does not sell or share any personally identifiable information with third parties with the exception of financial institutions or United States government agencies in cases where identity theft or fraud is suspected, or in the event the customers account is not within good standing for the purpose of debt collection.

## Non-Personally Identifiable Information

Phillips Data collects and uses some non-personally identifiable, generic information about our users as a means of measuring the effectiveness of our Web site. Phillips Data's servers identify certain user information in the normal course of operation, although such information does not reveal a user's personal identity. This information includes but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser types, operating systems, content accessed, and date and time of such access.

Phillips Data uses cookies to keep track of user sessions and to customize the user experience on our Web site. We do not store financial information or plain text passwords in cookies.

## Business Transfers

As we continue to grow and develop our business, we might sell or buy assets. In such transactions, customer information is generally considered a business asset. In the event that Phillips Data is acquired, information obtained from customers may be included as one of the transferred assets.

## Confidentiality and Security Safeguards

Phillips Data takes reasonable precautions to protect individually identifiable information against loss, misuse, alteration, unauthorized access and disclosure. Information is only accessible to authorized personnel who need it in order to perform their jobs.

## Disclosure Pursuant to Legal Process

Phillips Data reserves the right to release any information or data collected by or about a customer to any government agency or person upon search warrant, court order, subpoena, or any other legally binding means under the laws of the United States of America. Phillips Data may also allow access to this information under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of customers or the public or the safety and integrity of our Web site and servers.
